LINKS

Portfolio: www.itsmeleo.com

• LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/leolamnguyen/

SKILLS

Decision Making Web development projects
Adobe Creative Suite Advanced MS Office Suite

Problem resolution Web Design
Relationship development UX Design
Social Media Technologies HTML CSS

VOLUNTEER WORK

• 2015: The 7th European - Vietnamese Documentary Film Festival

2017: Toronto International Film Festival (TIFF)
2018: Toronto International Film Festival (TIFF)

EDUCATION

Post-Degree Certificate - Website Development • Humber College

Toronto, ON • 09/2022

Bachelor of Creative Advertising - Advertising · Humber College

Toronto, ON • 08/2021

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Performance-driven advertising/web design student motivated to solve all web-based needs. Have experience in creating designs, sample layouts and concepts and generating new ideas with limited direction. With superior work ethic and good teamwork, problem-solving and organizational skills. Proficient in developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Social Media Intern · Admission Hub

Toronto, ON • January 2021 to July 2021

- Responded to comments, posts and questions from various channels under the supervision of the Social Media Manager.
- Created engaging content to catch the attention of potential customers.
- Conducted daily updates to social media profiles to boost company online presence.
- Analyzed trends in social media posts and followers to maximize views.
- Created content strategies for digital media.

Marketing Intern · CheaprEats

Toronto, ON • June 2020 to August 2020

- Tracked and analyzed web analytics to recommend proactive adjustments to strategies.
- Worked with other team members to synchronize web presence with brand identity and logo.
- Designed graphics for websites, logos and promotions for marketing purposes.
- Collaborated with team members to help expand marketing channels.
- Performed market analysis and researched latest trends.

Marketing Intern · Campbell Immigration Law Firm

Toronto, ON • June 2019 to August 2019

- Contributed to mock-ups, email campaigns and social media content.
- Designed and presented social media campaign ideas.
- Stayed updated with the latest marketing concepts and techniques.
- Designed graphics for websites, logos and promotions for marketing purposes.
- Provided administrative support to senior staff including creating proposals and organizing documentation.